# Kaitlyn Majkoski

+44 7308719295 London kaitlyn.majkoski@gmail.com

## Political Intelligence Analyst

Website: kaitlynmyn LinkedIn: majkoski

A committed, knowledgeable and capable researcher with significant expertise in statistical analysis. Highly experienced in project and team management, strategic planning, and report-writing. A confident presenter, able to impart complex information to audiences of all levels. Currently working as a Political Intelligence Analyst, with a background in International Relations and experience across media consulting, stakeholder engagement, and business development.

### **SKILLS**

Tools and Languages Other Skills SPSS, R Programming, SQL, Tableau, Power BI

Data Collection, Visualization, and Analysis, Tutoring and Presenting, Peer Mentoring

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Political Intelligence Analyst | Dods Group

Feb 2024 — Present

 Provide high-quality political insight and research to clients, ensuring exceptional service through regular meetings and deliverables.

#### Media Consultant | Apollo Strategic Communications

Nov 2023 — Feb 2024

- Developed data-driven media strategies using in-depth research to help clients improve brand positioning and audience engagement.
- Synthesized complex information into actionable strategies for clients.

## Stakeholder Engagement Administrator | Tony Blair Institute

Oct 2023 — Jan 2024

• Maintained stakeholder data integrity in the CRM, running reports to identify gaps and ensure data quality across the organization.

## Business Development and Events Assistant | Milken Institute

Mar 2022 — Oct 2022

- Managed relationships with sponsors and corporate supporters for the Global Conference.
- Supported strategy development for Institute programs in Europe.

## Mayor's Office of International Affairs Intern | City of Los Angeles

May 2022 — Sep 2022

Conducted research to facilitate strategic partnerships between Hanoi and Los Angeles, focusing on collaboration opportunities.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **MSc in International Relations**

Sep 2022 — Aug 2023

The London School of Economics and Political Science (LSE)

- Thesis: Evaluation of Chinese Cyber Norm Promotion through the Digital Silk Road in Ethiopia.
- Supervisor: Professor William Callahan.

## Bachelor of Arts - BA, Political Science and Government

Aug 2019 - Dec 2021

University of Southern California

- Minor: French @ Dornsife College of Letters, Arts and Sciences.
- Specialization: Web Information & Technologies @ Viterbi School of Engineering.
- GPA: 3.96

#### **ACTIVITIES**

#### Activities

• Journal Reviewer, Millennium Journal of International Relations

Sep 2022 — Sep 2023

Simulation Administrator, LSE Future Impact Summit

Oct 2022

## **Honors & Awards**

USC Public Service Intern

Jun 2021

- Summer internship program where students worked 10 or 20 hours a week for 10 weeks at their JEP site.
- USC Gateway Intern

- Paid summer internship program with mentorship and career seminars.

May 2021

#### C-----

Introduction to Information Security (ITP 125)

May 2021

Web Publishing (ITP 104)

May 2021